[
    {
      "_id": "QZ101",
      "name": "Introduction to Rocket Propulsion",
      "description": "Basic principles of rocket propulsion and rocket engines.",
      "course": "674e3c7cf38066775326cb6d",
      "dateAvailable": "2024-11-26T11:59:59Z",
      "dateUnavailable": "2024-12-03T11:59:59Z",
      "dueDate": "2024-12-02T11:59:59Z",
      "questions": [
        {
          "_id": "QA101",
          "quiz": "QZ101",
          "title": "Easy Question",
          "type": "Multiple Choice",
          "points": 4,
          "question": "How much is 2 + 2?",
          "choices":[
            {
                "_id": "A101",
                "question": "QA101",
                "correct": false,
                "answer": 4
            },
            {
                "_id": "A102",
                "question": "QA101",
                "correct": false,
                "answer": 3
            },
            {
                "_id": "A103",
                "question": "QA101",
                "correct": true,
                "answer": 5
            },
            {
                "_id": "A104",
                "question": "QA101",
                "correct": false,
                "answer": 7
            }
          ]
        },
        {
            "_id": "QA102",
            "quiz": "QZ101",
            "title": "Is 2 + 2 = 4?",
            "type": "True/False",
            "points": 3,
            "question": "Is it true that 2 + 2 = 4?",
            "choices":[
              {
                  "_id": "A201",
                  "question": "QA102",
                  "correct": true,
                  "answer": "True"
              },
              {
                  "_id": "A202",
                  "question": "QA102",
                  "correct": false,
                  "answer": "False"
              }
            ]
          },
          {
            "_id": "QA103",
            "quiz": "QZ101",
            "title": "Easy fill in the blank",
            "type": "Fill In the Blank",
            "points": 4,
            "question": "How much is 2 + 2 = __________?",
            "choices":[
              {
                  "_id": "A301",
                  "question": "QA103",
                  "answer": "2"
              },
              {
                  "_id": "A302",
                  "question": "QA103",
                  "answer": "two"
              },
              {
                "_id": "A303",
                "question": "QA103",
                "answer": "dos"
            }
            ]
          }
      ]
    }
  ]